Voices collide, the storm and the flame. Laughter and chaos, it's part of the game.
Secrets unravel, the stage is alive. In Psyche's arena, the strange will survive.
Who's afraid?
Let it break from shadows to starlight
The truth will be shown
The psyche awakens
You're never alone
Expect the unexpected
Strange and unusual
Step inside the flow
The circus of shadows
It's Psyche's show
Terrible trolls in the dark
Take their stand, but angels are dancing
Torch light in hell
The psyches show terrible trolls in the dark, take their stand, the angels are dan-
What are you guys doing?
Oh
Friday day, not a bad day. I stopped by a couple chats. I was in KK's chat that I was in
Samhain's chat. This is addressing some, you know, some people going, you know, they're still talking about some of the silly stuff
I just went on to address it. It seems like it's like
In KK's, she was like, you know what, I can tell you feel maybe I was kind of jumping on the bandwagon a little bit.
She was like, you know, she was cool.
She might like still, you know, she has her own opinion, it's fine, but she was okay.
And then I went to Sandman, and then he like, just started, oh my god, oh my, no, you're, all your cats, I was like, yeah, well, one,
like Trix is not neutered, but all the other cats are fixed.
And it's like, he's really not the biggest, biggest.
I worry because he's not a female cat like that's what I'd be more concerned about fixing a female cat
So she like a pregnant because I've already had three letters of kittens and something like you know I
Think I'm time to yeah, I've got a good good group here. And so
No, but uh, I don't know they just were overreacting. I was like, you know, it's like, you know
Struggles for content it seems like so it's gonna let you
Let's you run your show and I just left so but anyway also, but I also watched a few Alex Mayer's
Clips I could you know what we're going on tomorrow. I can play this. This is the
The preview for tomorrow. Let me just pull it up in second
She created this and it's really cool
And if that yep, I'll play this wall. I can't so let's see. It's gonna be my
like videos
watch later, let's see, oh yeah here it is, okay so here it is, the screen, okay I can't
Hey, where's the streamer? Okay, so I have an open panel, but I should show you this real quick
So I can add stuff to the show now so I can go like this
I can go share screen and it go okay show a screen, and then I go to the window
There's the open window. I have too many open windows open. Let's look at it. One two three
Four
Share this screen, I think it's, oh here it is, okay got it, make sure that moves the screen
too.
So I get this perfect, oh here we go, perfect, enjoy this.
Hello? You see me? Hold on. Right there? Happen! Hold on. I'll figure it out.
You don't see me? Hold on.
Look for a special three-part series exclusively from IRN News Time, featuring special guest,
Psyche Awakens of the popular YouTube channel, Psyche Awakens Terror.
Psyche Awakens is an established and professional astrologer and tarot card reader who graciously
educates the public weekly through his life on hand. Tomorrow, August 24 at 12 p.m. Pacific
Standard Time, Psyche Awakens and I will discuss the origins of astrology and how it may indeed
of many Christians today. In addition, we will focus on the specific art angel who was said to
have taught astrology to humanity. See you live tomorrow.
Are you guys going to be there? Here's the link to the, here you go.
Come on up, go see.
Are you serious? Am I right now?
Where are you?
Hi. Hey Nancy.
But anyway, look, there he is. Finally.
You're host.
You hear me okay?
Yeah.
What's up, man?
What's up?
I said, what's up, man?
Oh, it's your little bit. You're a little bit loud.
Any better at all or no?
Do you want to come up, Shan?
We're talking in the back.
It's a little bit loud, though.
Be sure to please.
Like my voice is really loud?
Yeah.
Even if I felt like this was really loud?
I can probably fix it.
Hold on for a little bit.
And it might say, oh yeah, it's way too loud.
Hold on.
Fix it.
Yeah, oh, that's right. Oh shit
And that's right. Yeah, can you hear me test us? Yes? Yes? Yes? Yes? Good or loud?
Don't great. Oh, you really guess. This is thank you. You know what what you might be saying is that some beautiful?
That's regular regular
Hey, Revolver Viola. Hi. I'm not French. I'm not I'm not opulence and oh
How's like you doing? Is he okay? What's going on?
Do you guys think I'm right here?
He's doing good, bro.
Oh, there he is.
Doing well. He's doing well.
All right. I've been here.
Oh, my nigga.
All right.
Wait, hold on to one white man.
Oh, are you part Native American?
It's always bothered me about you.
Like you have a good look to you overall.
But like, are you fucking part Native American?
I got to know.
Um, well, like the DNA tests are coming out with some like
I think there's like tiny like little percentages of maybe perhaps like Native American like I think it was less than 1% though
So it's like you don't really
Yeah, you are freaking me out
Yeah, I'm very like I'm very 60% like you you're up. It's like actually that 100% European like Western European basically
But it's you know, you're the perfect area in prototype if only you like pussy. That's so good
How's it going, man? I should do bro. I shamed for 13 hours
I'm gonna cried like I once to the end slowly f-slur. I cried like an f-slur. I would hope not you don't fuck
No, I did I'm fucking I'm fucking on your screen
Yeah, you did who the fuck it way who's talk who was this asshole talking not showing its face
Who the fuck are you asshole will show your face
Shoot you have to say bro
Okay, it's an open panel. Well, that's fair. I mean, if you don't give a fuck what I have to say, that's fair
I'm talking to you until you show your face. It's an open panel. I don't know. That's really rude. It's so psychical. Yeah, man
You're not gonna talk over it. You're not gonna cover it. I
Renewed two of my insurance licenses in Florida. You know, if you're making a bit of coin that's good for you
I've been drinking a lot and eating less. So mama's gonna get the
already got already got it nigga you want to see no wait hold on don't worry about it hold on
all right all right you want to see it wait hold on no hold on hold on
let me psyche real quick just give me permission if that's what you need to make sure you do it
asshole i don't know who the fuck you are i wasn't well that's that's okay i mean that's
So thank you for being polite about it. It's like you just give me permission. Yeah, you're just fucking suck dude
Well, that's like you give me permission. Yeah, you're fucking powered you piece of shit shut your bitch ass up nigger
Hello IQ month
This is why I told you that dude
Give me fucking permission, dude.
This guy's an asshole with nothing.
He's always nothing.
Yeah, you just said that and you just broke TOS.
Hey, I'm not talking to you, asshole.
I don't give a fuck who you're talking to.
You just broke TOS.
I'm not talking to you, asshole.
You just said the N word. You don't fuck.
Fuck this asshole.
You double down. You double down twice.
You double down. How's it go? I'm not I don't get a shoot you just a matter of fact you do it again
You're going so good. You're going so you're going so again. How's it going so again? Let's go fuck you again. You're gone
I'm gonna actually go to a
You were showed tomorrow called IRL news time with Alexander Meyers and
She's really cool. And so I recommend everybody check out tomorrow 12 p.m. Pacific Standard Time and
I'll watch it. You watch it. Oh
Okay, thank you. All right, I like pussy what I finally pussy what
If only you like to see what a perfect area. Hey T why listen man if you want to talk that's cool, bro
All right, I'm not gonna fucking
You're not gonna fucking talk over me asshole, you're not gonna talk over me nigger, okay
Don't kick me off
Okay, what is it tomorrow at 1.40 p.m. I'll see it man. Yeah, Florida time. I got to my insurance like
3 p.m. On a IRL news time like it's just so sad you're not in the pussy you'd be the perfectarian man
I've told you I would I would that would be a whole different
It would be a whole different thing. All right now see why go ahead and talk go ahead and talk
I'm not a total asshole go ahead and talk man. Well, I don't think you're a total psyche. Can I speak?
Can I speak or yes or no? I don't think you're a total asshole. I think you I think you you're a total retard
That's I personally that's my thing. I think that you're too drunk. You don't let the fuck you're talking about your sling your words
You have no idea what you're talking about
Like what what are you can I actually ask you like I'm not even trying to bet you are nothing like yeah
No, that's fine. If we're talking
That's a good question. Yeah, go ahead and show yourself. Yeah, that's fine. Dude. What's up, man?
I I probably was I didn't show myself. I'm dumb. I'm over here top right
Oh, I see you. I see you dude. I'm not that drunk girl. Yeah, I got you you were talking shit earlier, but go ahead
Yeah, I was because he kept interrupting me dude. Like I'm just talking. Yeah, I used to troll this guy man
I'm trying to be nice. I got you used to troll this guy, but you're not gonna do any more
That's the thing though. I mean you can troll this guy. Yeah, I don't feel like all you want because
Yeah, I'm going sorry. I don't want to interrupt you so go ahead
Well, listen, you share your words, you know what the fuck you're talking about you stupid ass
Yeah, dude, I don't understand what you just said that like dude
I've been doing my own stream and shit and and you said that word. Yeah, you shouldn't even be up here
I mean, that's Martin. You know, oh, yeah, no one could say the n-word
In his heart he believes in free speech and lets you up here. Yeah, he lets me up here. So what's your fucking problem?
See why I was so they he's trippin out
No, we can talk. We can talk. We can talk. We can talk. We can talk man to man. We're so good in our heart
We let you have a free speech who what do you what are you passionate about? Yeah, not when you say the n word though
Come fuck you don't like oh, you don't like the the niggard. Okay?
So I won't get him. I thought that I thought that
Again, that's why I got you by the way. I got you
You got me recorded asshole good. I don't know what you look like and I don't really care. Yeah, you're gone
Oh, okay. He's a fucking piece of shit. All right. That's how you want to do it. You're a little coward your little baby
You know I insulted this
Okay, okay, okay, Nick. Okay, Nick slur. I'm gonna have to kick listen
No, you're worse than a fucking, uh, uh, cigarette, a fog, a slur, right?
Listen, I am sold to this guy's dad, and I apologize for it, and he was man enough to have me buck up on her.
You were drunk and truck, you don't look like a fucking fucking fucking faceless piece of shit.
You're a faceless piece of shit, nigga.
So suck it, bitch, asshole.
Fuck you.
Psyche go ahead
So then we could talk about this another time that you're a fucking baby until then and go ahead Psyche go ahead
Oh, I didn't know we can break. Well, I
School is cool, bro
I hope you guys were having a good weekend, jeez, I mean
There's there's a show the channels posted in the chat for my peers tomorrow
I heard your friends with Alexander, aren't you LD?
What?
Your friends with Alexander mayors. I'm fucking if they can say slurs. I'm finna say I've known Alex
I've known Alex a very long time. Give me an argument, bro
Like yeah, I've met her before I've met Alex before your argument is you shouldn't come on his
panel and say slurs because you know
Man, what are we debating bro, is sorry
I just gave you the debate you I just gave you
She had nice things to say about you and you know
with her tomorrow. We're doing like a three-part series together. Oh cool. Yeah, you can if you
want to see it's at noon tomorrow on her show. I gotta work. I gotta work. Well just watch,
make sure you watch the replay, you know. Yeah, yeah, I'll definitely check it out. Yeah, no,
I've met, I've met Alex before. I've known Alex a long time. She said you went to Vegas together,
you actually met in person, right? I was living in Vegas and she came out there and yeah, we've
met and, you know, had food and smoked a joint or something, I forget.
but this dude has a great mustache by the way psyche you know that mr. ld you can hate my ass i don't give a fucking
and you would say you have a great mustache sir you have a great fucking
Mine looks like shit, mine looks like shit, it looks like shit, it looks like shit, mine looks like shit, mine looks like shit, mine looks like shit, mine looks like shit, mine looks like shit, mine looks like shit, mine looks like shit, mine looks like shit, mine looks like shit, mine looks like shit, mine looks like shit, mine looks like shit, mine looks like shit, mine looks like shit, mine looks like shit, mine looks like shit, mine looks like shit, mine looks like shit, mine looks like shit, mine looks like shit, mine looks like shit, mine looks like shit, mine looks like shit, mine looks like shit, mine looks like shit, mine looks like shit, mine looks like shit, mine looks like shit, mine looks like shit, mine looks like shit, mine looks like shit, mine looks like shit, mine looks like shit, mine looks like shit, mine looks like shit, mine looks like shit, mine looks like shit, mine looks like shit, mine looks like shit, mine looks like shit, mine looks like
all right anyway great must ask for this man because you don't know what the fuck you're talking about
i will talk to you dude i'm trying i'm being nice to you bro because like i don't have to be
mature another white man i will do it i'll give you i will go in the back chat and give you my
telegram so if you don't have to go in the back chat we're both here so what do you want to debate
I really offended you. Sorry, dude. Shit. No, let's run that bitch dog. It's for vile or deep, bro
At me. It's okay. You get it. You get it. Okay. You don't know what the fuck you're talking about. You just drunk
What am I not? What do I not know what I'm talking about, man? Real quick. Like
I don't even know what you're saying
You literally have to say what you're saying without slurring your words. I've been drunk for 13 hours, mate
I've been drunk for therefore I win Ari. I want that fucking debate. All right, never mind
I guess you did because you haven't been drunk for 13 hours. Yeah
I haven't
And you're
Let's take it back. Hey retract it
How much have you drank?
What I said was you've been slurring your words. You said for 13 hours an hour. I don't get it. It's like
two hour one hour you've been slurring your word but therefore you're drunk retard but you said 13 hours
well you're never gonna
All right, go ahead. I'm done. Yeah, dude. Yeah, I'm never gonna what you don't know what to do for living real come on
Anyway, this is like a stream. They're not gonna be drunk for a living
Hey, man, hey, man without calling you an asshole or an ensler you got my tell me whatever you want my hit my hit my
Telegram up motherfucker. You don't want it. You don't want the debate. Yeah, go ahead. No coward. Do it do it
We're wild or deep you don't wanna
I know I did get it and I'm going to leave it alone.
I did win but leave it alone.
This guy's an asshole.
It's like he's being a lead alone.
I won.
You need to win with autism asshole.
I give you my telegram.
You won't fucking debate me.
Go ahead.
What the fuck is a telegram?
You're going to start to be like smoke your life. Do you want to actually debate? Well, you should be gone by the way
Yeah, yeah, I'm gonna have
Baby have your daddy. Oh, do you want some have your daddy's like you boot me you little
All right, asshole, I don't know what the fuck
Hey man, you've already been in your seeded
Revilardz, I'm showing my ugly old face
You can fucking see me asshole, I'm Revilardz on Telegram, nigga
Don't fucking get it twisted, yeah
Anyway, nice mustache, what's up, Psych?
What's going on, bro? I'm gonna ignore this asshole guy now
I wouldn't do that if I was you
Well, does he get in your ammo?
Yeah, he'll watch a bowler
We're seeing it with ghosty and the LD and
We're here earlier. Yeah, I mean you guys did talk shit about my dude. Uh, so like though
they did
Who?
Who did where I'm where? Oh
Yeah, we're talking about and what I'll be definitely you definitely I actually know you
I talked shit about like
Did you not did you wear wear and when?
Not tonight dad. You did you never talk about a day? Why are you just making up shit T? Why fuck you never you never said that
Never said what?
You never talked shit about psyche. No, you actually know you for real. I don't know
Like honestly, I don't I don't do that shit
I did T.Y. I did and like the guys big enough to have me back in this town
You gotta admit T.Y. as much problems as you and I have
Well, Saiki loves that. That's his brother. He loves everybody though.
Hey man, come on man. Have some love in here.
I don't know. This LD nigger has a good mustache.
You gotta know that. Come on man.
I mean, it's a pretty nice mustache.
It is a nice mustache.
It is a nice mustache. There you go.
looks like an uniting people even if people don't hate me other
national socialists that fucking hate me yeah i'm
i model i model my mustache after stalin
i'm not a big fan i gotta i gotta say i'm not a big fan i'm not a big fan
not a big fan oh no i'm not a big fan of the communist party yeah i'm more of a fascist
You know, I'm like for the workers
But you don't look at what the nox do to our people bro. It's okay. I've read
I've read I've read
Duff's coffee towel angles and all that shit. It's interesting. It's your hair. That's what you should read read some Karl Marx
I have read Karl Marx
So it's not the deer. It's your wife. I'm sorry. I cut you off to you. I go ahead dude
Yeah, go ahead my I cut you off good
No, bro
Like I think you're gonna say the same thing about this guy that he's such a great like piece of potential
But he's only stuck on the bourgeoisie and not race and he can't see pasta
But I don't want to imbue my thoughts on you
You're gonna have me or the other year goes
Yeah, it's all about LD. It's like he's just a generic. No offense. No offense, hon
You're on his you're on his panel though. I know man, but if you feel like this guy
No, if you've been a man by the way, second of all, you're talking about him. So if you're a lot of should have talked about him
Go ahead and talk it says fucking panel. I did it allows you to be up here. I'm talking about the guy
That's like like talking about asshole Stalin like he's he's uh some humanitarian
Did you not say I don't give no all I said all I say was that I follow my mustache. Listen, we are gonna have a date. Did you just say psyche?
Dude, I'm sorry bro. Like I apparently like I don't know you guys got something going on. I'll leave it alone. I'm sorry. I'm just a drunken
the
in some ways yeah in some ways you are returning somewhat you're really angry
about this aren't you all right all right dead-end slurred you know that you want telegram
hit me on telegram shut the fuck up dude okay that's cool that's between tell me on telegram
how you really feel that's not the newest psyche that's between me and you we can have a debate
that's what does it have to do with psyche it's not psyche's not on telegram do what you're talking about
It is. Yeah. Asshole. Nice ad hominem. Okay. So what what? Okay. There you go. That's a logical and dumb ass. You're very butter. You said the N word.
Yeah, I know you hate them too. They're not human. That's cool. Yeah, go ahead. Okay. All right. You're really butthurt
Wow, miss Stacy. I really miss you off. I'm so sorry
The word I mean, yeah
Face
You see my ugly old face and my fucking return address
with Ravine, I live in Cape Coral, Florida,
but I don't know anything about you, but that's okay.
And you can be a coward, maybe all you want, bro.
Come and kill me, that's cool, dude.
That's cool, bro.
No, it's fine, it's fine.
It's all right, hit me up until the end, bro.
Tell me what you want to say.
It's free speech. You can say whatever you want. So what's the problem? I don't support free speech. I'm a fascist
Well, there's not there's not free
You're up here and psyche log he's letting you up here is he not no he doesn't love me we have a very
What he's letting you up here is he?
Okay, he's not let you up here
I gave bro, I gave them
What am I talking about?
That's what I want to do in work
When you get enough from prom with me built up you can message me cuz I
Yeah
All right, that makes you feel better at night dude how much should I talk to actually be a puppy dumb fuck
Why don't you show yourself? I'm curious. Thank you. Why doesn't this guy show himself? Yeah, I'll show myself
I was very curious. I'm just curious. I'm done to run one. We're sure when our fucking selves are ugly old fuck